CASON QUISENBERRY

E: casonq23@gmail.com A: College Station, TX 77801

WWW: casonquisenberry.myportfolio.com

| PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced in creating games while working both in a team and individually. Using a combination of game design and programming to create a variety of projects. Experienced in working on multiple projects simultaneously, and balancing the workload accordingly.

WORK HISTORY

Texas A&M University - Student Teacher

College Station, TX • 06/2023 - Current

Assisting students enrolled in VIST-206, Principles of Design III. Students work in groups to create a video game using Unreal Engine 5, and I provide programming help, debugging, and general feedback. Give lectures and technical demonstrations that an over both Unreal 5 and game design.

Soft Interaction Lab - Unreal Research Assistant

College Station, TX • 04/2023 - Current

Responsible for designing and developing systems and tools to create educational learning simulations using Unreal 4 and 5. Work with both virtual reality and flat simulations to help educate nursing students at Texas A&M University. Worked and communicated in two different teams of 5 in order to meet the client's needs.

Buena Vista Wildlife Safari And RV Park - Web Developer

Remote • 05/2021 - 08/2022

Programmed and designed a website relaunch for Buena Vista Safari, a local small business in central Texas. Worked and communicated with a team of five to create a custom website for the client. Prototyped the base website and programmed each major feature of the website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

| PROJECTS

Mock Trial Simulation | Soft Interaction Lab

April 2023 - Current

- Working to create a simulation that nurses can use to train themselves on how to testified in court.
- Implemented a speech recognition program, and created a system that processes that data to have player and Al interaction.
- Designed the flow and structure of the simulation as well as writing the dialogue for the Al actors.

VR Forensic Nursing | Soft Interaction Lab

June 2023 - Current

- Working to create a forensic nursing simulation that helps nurses go over the procedure for head-to-toe examinations.
- Debugged various systems, including animations, UI, audio, and structure, to get the project ready for shipping.
- Creating new training modules for the project that involved player interaction, physics interactions, animation systems, UI, and design work.

SKILLS

- C. C++
- · Unreal Engine 4 & 5
- Unreal Blueprints
- Gameplay Programming
- Python
- VR Development
- Game Design
- Whiteboxing
- · Asset Implementation
- Git/Github
- Plastic SCM

| EDUCATION

Texas A&M University

College Station, TX • Expected in 05/2024

Bachelor of Science: Visualization degree with a focus on video game development with a minor in game design. Worked with groups of other students to make and develop games, and learned development skills and 3D software for a variety of different courses.